Guide to the Alaska Commercial Company Records, 1868-1940 JL006
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1. General Accounts: Papers, 1888 - 1940
  - Subseries B. Accounts, 1890 - 1939
    - Accounts 247 - 250, 1910 - 1913 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - 247 Freight and passenger contracts, 1910
      - 248 Alaska Coast Co., 1912-1913
      - 249 Alaska Pacific Express Co., 1910
      - 250 "Glory of the Seas", 1910
    - Accounts 251 - 256, 1909 - 1914 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - 251 Receipt for register-"Tonquin", 1910
      - 252 Bill of sale-Cook Inlet Transportation Co., 1909
      - 253 "Rupert City"-charter party, 1910
      - 254 Accident- N. Rapin, 1910
      - 255 SS "Farallon" loss, 1910
      - 256 Victor Talking Machine Co., 1913-1914
    - Accounts 257 - 260, 1904 - 1913 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - 257 Annie Scanlan-note and mortgage, 1904-1910
      - 258 "Allen A"-charter party, 1910
      - 259 William Murphy, 1910-1912
      - 260 Willard B. Hastings, 1908-1913
    - Account 261: Capt. C.E. Radclyffe, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Account 263: Alaska Coast Commercial Co., 1906-1907 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Account 263: Alaska Coast Commercial Co., 1906-1907 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Accounts 264 - 269, 1910-1913 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - 264 Sale of Hope Station buildings, 1910-1912
      - 266 Cache Creek Mining Co., 1910-1911
      - 267 John Schmidt, 1910-1911
      - 268 Canadian Collieries Ltd- agreement, 1911-1913
      - 269 "Jeanie"-loss, 1910
    - Accounts 270 -271, 1904; 1911 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - 270 O.W. Carlson- power of attorney, 1904
      - 271 Bruce Lloyd, 1911
    - Account 272: "Glory of the Seas", 1910-1911 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Account 273: "Glory of the Seas", 1910 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Accounts 274 - 275, 1909 - 1911 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - 274 Cooke and Lake, 1909-1910
      - 275 W.P. O'Erien -vs- A.C.Co., 1910-1911
    - Accounts 276 - 281, 1908 - 1911 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - 276 Bureau of Fisheries, 1910
      - 278 "Alice" and "Susitna"- sale, 1911
      - 279 Sundry bills-Blodgett and Herbert, 1908-1910
      - 280 SS "Titania"- charter party, 1911
      - 281 "Ida McKay"- charter party, 1911
    - Accounts 282 - 284, 1910 - 1911 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - 282 Contracts of employees, 1910
      - 283 Sale agreement- stock of merchandise at Susitna, 1911
      - 284 Cook Inlet Transportation Co., 1911
    - Accounts 285 - 291, 1907 - 1911 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - 285 "S.B. Mathews"- blueprints, plans, 1907-1909
      - 286 "Hunter" machinery, 1908-1909
      - 289 J.W. Alley- agreement, 1911
      - 290 Joseph F. Buike, 1911
      - 291 Carl Frank, 1911
    - Account 292: Sixty Mile Syndicate, 1906 - 1907 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Account 293 - 297, 1900 - 1913 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - 293 Saw Mill (Yukon), 1907
      - 294 Stockholders- Alaska Packers Association, 1904-1907
      - 295 Reports, charters- "St. Paul" and "Portland", 1900
      - 296 Estate of Al Nene, 1907
      - 297 S.F. Cottle, 1911-1913
    - Account 298: SS "Meteor"- charter, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Account 299: Proof of loss- "Portland" claim [1 of 2], 1910-1913 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Account 299: Proof of loss- "Portland" claim [2 of 2], 1910-1913 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Account 300 - 304, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - 300 Quitclaim deed tJ.A. Silverman, 1911
      - 301 Tyoonak building- bill of sale, 1911
      - 302 Death of native at Unalaska, 1911
      - 303 "Lina K"- sale, 1911
      - 304 Frank Wills, 1911
    - Account 305 - 308, 1911 - 1914 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - 305 William Brown estate, 1911-1914
      - 306 Deadwood Creek Circle- bill of sale, 1911
      - 307 Sale of Port Graham tAlaska Coast Co., 1911-1913
      - 308 John J. Folstad, J.J. Diggs, 1911
    - Account 309 - 310, 1911 - 1914 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - 309 Carrie Koester, 1911-1914
      - 310 Cohn Boys, 1912-1914
    - Account 311 - 314, 1910 - 1912 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - 311 C.P. Morgan, 1910-1912
      - 312 Alaska Steamship Co., 1912
      - 313 Yukon Saw Mill contract, 1911
      - 314 William McPhee, 1912
    - Account 315: Louis Greenbaum, 1902 - 1912 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Accounts 315A - 322, 1899 - 1919 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - 315a Arthur Harper estate, 1919
      - 316 Scandanavian American Bank, 1912
      - 317 Capt. August Dahlquist, 1911-1912
      - 318 "Robert R. Hind"- charter party, 1912
      - 319 Sunrise plant- bill of sale, 1912
      - 320 Natalia Clark, 1899
      - 321 James M. Wilson, 1897
      - 322 "Rupert City"- charter party, 1912
    - Account 323: "Lettie"- sale, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Accounts 324 - 326, 1912 - 1918 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - 324 Barge "St. James"- charter, 1912
      - 325 Afognak Station- bill of sale, 1912
      - 326 A.C. Goss, 1912-1918
    - Account 327: Launch "The Moravian", 1912 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Accounts 328 - 333, 1910 - 1918 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - 328 Thomas A. McGowen- power of attorney, 1912
      - 329 U.S. Army Quartermaster contract for coal, 1912
      - 330 C.S. Carter order, 1911-1912
      - 331 M.L. Washburn estate, final account, 1912 - 1918
      - 332 Mrs. M. Dowd, 1912
      - 333 John A. Anderson, 1910-1912
    - Account 334: M.L. Washburn estate, sundry papers, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Account 336 - 339, 1911 - 1913 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - 336 David Brown, 1911
      - 337 Mrs. E.H. Mann, 1913
      - 338 "Rupert City"- charter party, 1913
      - 339 Eastman Kodak- order instructions, 1913
    - Account 342: "Leelanow"- charter party, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Account 343: "Christian Bros."- charter party, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Accounts 344 - 349, 1909 - 1914 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - 344 George Levitt- will, 1906-1913
      - 345 B.C. Mickle, J.C. Fred Lowrie, 1909
      - 346 Data re: analysis of coal, 1909-1913
      - 347 "Henrik Ibsen"- charter, 1914
      - 349 "Ethel Zane"- charter party, 1914
    - Accounts 350 - 356, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - 350 "Ariel"- charter party, 1914
      - 351 Consent tact as agent of the A.C.Co., 1914
      - 352 Consent tact as agent of the ApollConsolidated Mining Co., 1914
      - 353 Delarof Development Co.- statement, 1914
      - 354 Consent tact as agent of the Delarof Developemtn Co., 1914
      - 355 Sloss Securities Co., 1914
      - 356 Northern Navigation Co.- sale tAmerican Yukon Navigation Co., 1914
    - Accounts 358: Statements to banks, 1922-1930 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Accounts 358A: Statements to banks, 1930 - 1931 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Accounts 358B: Statements to banks, 1914 - 1932 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Accounts 359: Plot of A.C. Co. property- St. Michael, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Accounts 360: Drew Mine, 1899-1902 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Accounts 361 - 364, 1899-1902 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - 361 Memfrom W.H. Fairbanks, n.d.
      - 362 Timber licenses, 1914
      - 363 Fletcher's order from Erskine, 1913
      - 364 McNally and Maitland- agreement, 1914-1915
    - Accounts 365 - 366, 1903-1916 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - 365 Julius Christensen- Kodiak, 1903-1916
      - 366 W.J. Erskine Co. sale of salt salmon, Seal Islands, 1914-1915
    - Accounts 367: Dawson Yukon Territory real estate; maps on Yukon Saw Mill, 1906-1917 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Accounts 369: John G. Blair account, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Accounts 370: Yukon Saw Mill Co.- sale and sundry correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Accounts 371 - 374, 1909-1916 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - 371 Annie Hemmingway, 1915
      - 372 J.B. Dyer, 1909-1911
      - 373 Contracts for hauling freight, 1915-1916
      - 374 W.J. Erskine Co.- Kodiak, statements, 1915-1916
    - Accounts 375 - 379, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - 375 W.J. Erskine, Washington trip report, 1916
      - 376 Data in re: proposal of Erskine Co. for furnishing pipe, etc., U.S. Fisheries Station, 1916
      - 377 Schooner "Harold Blekum", 1916
      - 378 Coal at Unalaska, 1916
      - 379 Beluga Whaling Co., 1916
    - Account 380: Brown & Hawkins, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Accounts 381 - 385, 1914 - 1916 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - 381 "Harold Blekum", 1916
      - 382 Dawson property, 1916
      - 383 Sale of Saw Mill, 1914-1915
      - 384 Dr. Alfred Thompson, 1915
      - 385 Agreement re: creditors, 1916
    - Accounts 386 - 395, 1916 - 1924 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - 386 McNally- sale agreement, 1916-1917
      - 387 Fleishbacker, Gerstle - agreement, 1917
      - 388 S. Applegate, 1917
      - 389 J.A. Herbert, 1916-1917
      - 390 Proxies- annual meeting, 1917 and 1924
      - 391 C.E. Lindquist account, 1917
      - 393 Susitna buildings- bill of sale, 1917
      - 394 Furniture inventory, 1917
      - 395 Louis F. Cooke, 1918
    - Accounts 396 - 405, 1917 - 1919 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - 396 Flag trademark- consent tuse, 1917
      - 397 Annie Hemmingway account, 1917
      - 398 McGowan Treadgold Co., 1917-1918
      - 399 American Yukon Navigation Co. deed, 1918
      - 400 License tpurchase explosives, 1918
      - 401 Beluga Whaling Co. deed, 1918
      - 402 "Lina K"- bill of sale mem, 1918
      - 403 Mail schedule- Unalaska and Kodiak, 1918
      - 405 Judge Sloss- order, 1919
    - Accounts 406 - 409, 1876 - 1919 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 406 Ernest Hennig estate, 1876-1899
      - 407 William Brown estate, 1900
      - 408 Mexican Ore Reduction Co. stock, 1900
      - 409 Prime furs from Alaska, 1919
    - Account 411: Inventory [1 of 2], 1918 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Account 411: Inventory [2 of 2], 1918 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Accounts 412 - 416, 1897 - 1920 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - 412 William P. Todd, 1917-1918
      - 413 Fur sale, 1919
      - 414 E.K. Pedler elected treasurer, 1919
      - 415 Articles of incorporation, A.C. Co., 1897-1932
      - 416 Charter party- "Carolyn Francis", 1920
    - Accounts 417 - 420, 1919 - 1921 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - 417 "City of Sydney"- charter, 1920
      - 418 W.J. Erskine Co.- fiscal statement, year ended, Nov. 30, 1919
      - 419 Reports State Commission of Corporations, 1920
      - 420 "MS Oznio"- charter, 1920-1921
    - Accounts 421 - 427, 1916 - 1921 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - 421 General Petroleum Co., 1916
      - 423 Warren K. Merritt matter, 1916-1920
      - 424 Dowd estate, 1920
      - 425 "City of Sydney"- coal contract, 1909 and 1920
      - 426 Crow Creek Consolidated Gold Mining Co. (Paul Buckley account), 1904-1907
      - 427 Henry Dirks' grandchildren- Kodiak, 1920-1921
    - Accounts 428 - 429, 1920 - 1921 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - 428 "Sequoia"- charter, 1921
      - 429 "Oregon"- bill of sale (also surveyors' reports), 1920-1921
    - Accounts 430 - 434, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - 430 "Oregon"-seaworthiness reports; loading fish; Bering Sea Fisheries Co., 1921
      - 431 George E. Butler, 1921
      - 432 Atlas Mercantile Co., 1921
      - 433 Board of Directors' meeting, 1921
      - 434 Cargstatements- voyage of M/S "Oregon", 1921
    - Accounts 435 - 436, 1913 - 1922 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - 435 Lester Herrick & Herrick- sundry reports, 1913-1922
      - 436 Stockholders' assent tthe amendment of the articles of incorporation, 1921
    - Account 437: "Apollo" charter Allen Holubar- 1922 and Universal Film Manufacturing 1923, 1922 - 1923 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Accounts 438 - 441, 1917 - 1922 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - 438 Northern Commercial Co.- waiver and consent tliquidation, 1922
      - 439 Liberty loans, 1917-1919
      - 440 Resolution tborrow from Wells FargNevada National Bank, 1922
      - 441 Commissioner of Internal Revenue Questionaire (affiliated corporations), 1919-1922
    - Account 442: Wharf reports and manifests- SS "Brookdale" shipment, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Account 443: James F. Burke estate- sundry papers, 1900-1916 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Accounts 444 - 453, 1900-1916 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - 444 Annual meeting notice, 1921-1922
      - 446 Sea otter affidavit, 1919
      - 447 W.J. Erskine Co. and Kodiak Fisheries Co., 1922
      - 448 Dexter Horton and Angland London and Paris National Bank, 1922-1926
      - 449 Customs- power of attorney tJ.L. Burnside from A.C.Co., 1923
      - 450 Bond applications, employees, 1923-1924
      - 452 Alaska Pioneer Oil Co., 1913-1921
      - 453 Officers and directors- W.J. Erskine Co., 1922-1923
    - Accounts 454 - 456, 1922-1923 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - 454 Point Judith Manifest cargo, 1923
      - 455 Inventory- stores' equipment, "Apollo", 1923
      - 456 Mortgage- "Everett Hays", 1922-1923
    - Accounts 457 - 461, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - 457 Boulder Hill Mining property, 1923-1926
      - 458 N. Gray- indebtedness, 1923
      - 460 Values- Northern Commercial Co. and stock-A.C.Co., 1923
      - 461 MS "Apollo"- sale, 1924
    - Account 462: Designations of agents for legal service in Alaska, 1924-1935 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Accounts 463 - 464, 1892 - 1924 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - 463 Quitclaim deed- J.A. Jacobson, 1892
      - 464 SS "Tiverton"- manifest (and "Brookdale") freight, 1924
    - Accounts 465 - 466, 1924 - 1925 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - 465 Standard Oil Co. and W.J. Erskine Co.- lease, 1924
      - 466 W.J. Erskine- sundry papers re: life insurance, 1924-1925
    - Account 467: "Griffdu"- charter, manifests, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Accounts 468 - 472, 1923 - 1927 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - 468 Iditarod and Ruby Telephone Companies, dates of dissolution, 1925
      - 469 Air Reduction Sales Co.- contract, 1925
      - 470 Alaska Game Laws, 1925
      - 471 J.L. Burnside- authority to sign checks, 1925
      - 472 Dividend distribution, 1923-1927
      - 472a Fur dealers' license, 1925
    - Accounts 473 - 474, 1921 - 1926 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - 473 John Kelly, James Cody- Northern Commercial Co. collections; consent of agents, 1921-26
      - 474 "Brookdale"- manifest of carg, 1926
    - Accounts 475 - 478, 1914 - 1927 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - 475 Northern Commercial Co.- assignments as trustee; memo- stock issue, 1914-1926
      - 476 International Banking Corporation, 1926
      - 478 Fur and fisheries laws, 1920-1927
    - Accounts 479 - 482, 1911 - 1927 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - 479 Petellin settlement, 1911
      - 480 Inventory- furniture and fixtures, 1926
      - 482 Eastman Kodak Co., 1927
    - Accounts 483 - 489, 1875 - 1931 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - 483 The Cope Estate (Henry P. Cope), 1875-1913
      - 484 Charles Grimm- signature on drafts tpost-master of Seattle, 1927-1931
      - 485 A.C. Goss- Fox Islands in Alaska, 1927
      - 486 Deed- Forty Mile, 1927
      - 489 MS "Ozmo"- bill of sale, 1919
    - Accounts 490 - 495, 1914 - 1931 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - 490 Western Alaska Steamship Co. - demand note, 1914
      - 491 Northern Commercial Co.- receipt for 4000 shares in the company, 1925
      - 493 Oakland Bank of Savings, 1920
      - 494 H.E. Riley- receipt for liberty bonds, 1922
      - 495 Aleutian Livestock Co., 1927
    - Account 496: H.E. Cope Estate- final settlement, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Accounts 498 - 503, 1928 - 1929 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - 498 Alaska Salmon Co.- lease with A.C.Co., 1928
      - 499 Hugh Hoben- contract, 1928
      - 500 J.R. Heldring- contract, 1928
      - 501 John H. Kelly- assignment
      - 502 Forms for use at Unalaska, 1928
      - 503 O.K. Quean, C.P. Hale-Unalaska
    - Account 503A: O.K. Quean, C.P. Hale-Unalaska, 1928 - 1929 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Account 503B: O.K. Quean, C.P. Hale-Unalaska, 1907 - 1928 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Accounts 504 - 507, 1923 - 1928 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - 504 Applegate property- deeds, 1923-1928
      - 506 "Eunice"- A.C. Goss account, 1925-1928
      - 507 Natalie Melividov estate, Ivan Olgin, administrator, 1928
      - 508 "Eunice"- bill of sale A.C. Goss, 1928
    - Accounts 509 - 514, 1928 - 1929 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - 509 McGlashan- deed, 1900-1930
      - 510 Jack Martin- contract Alaska Salmon Store at Unalaska, 1928
      - 511 Herring Fishers- contract, Unalaska, 1928
      - 512 Wharf schedule for livestock, 1928
      - 513 Yamashita Shipping Co., 1928
      - 514 Louis Strauss- deed, 1928-1929
    - Accounts 515 - 529, 1928 - 1929 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - 515 A.C. Goss- agreement with A.C.Co., 1928
      - 516 Mrs. A.C. Goss, 1928
      - 517 Aleutian Fur Co. and A.C. Goss Co., 1930
      - 518 C. Paladin contract, 1929
      - 519 Paul Willis- contract, 1929
      - 521 "El Cedro"- contract, 1929
      - 522 Stephan Moriss - bill of sale, 1929
      - 523 Francis Mandregan- bill of sale, 1929
      - 524 RussGreek church- Unalaska agreement, 1915
      - 525 W.L. Stuttaford- contract, 1929
      - 527 Durell Finch- bill of sale, 1929
      - 529 Harry S. Riley- contract, 1929
    - Account 530: North American Fisheries Inc. -1929 and herring contracts and operations 1931, 1929 - 1931 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Accounts 531 - 536, 1928 - 1931 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - 531 Hammond Lumber Co. at Dutch Harbor, 1929
      - 532 H.E. Bowman- quitclaim, 1928-1929
      - 533 T.E. Lawson- contract, 1929
      - 534 Louis Carp- agreement, 1929-1931
      - 536 Fresh Water Lake- Dutch Harbor Island, 1929
    - Accounts 537 - 545, 1929 - 1934 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - 537 Polar Packaging Co.- agreement, 1929
      - 538 Bid for carrying mail, 1929-1934
      - 539 "Eunice"- machinery data, 1929-1931
      - 540 Victor Corporation- contract, 1929-1930
      - 541 List of buildings at Unalaska, 1924-1929
      - 542 James Griffiths & Co.- freighting contract, 1930
      - 543 A.D. Kneip, 1930
      - 544 Private Cost Marks, 1929
      - 545 J.H. Broder- transfer building, 1929
    - Account 546: Herring Fishing contracts 1930-1932, 1929 - 1934 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Accounts 547 - 555, 1927 - 1934 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - 547 Jordan Columbus, Nick Creevden & Fritz Mustomen- agreement, 1930
      - 548 Fair Pool- Albert Lind, 1930
      - 549 Permit from War Department for Dutch Harbor wharves, 1930
      - 550 Permit War Department for Alaska Salmon Co., 1930
      - 551 Dockage and wharfage rates- Unalaska and Dutch Harbor, 1930
      - 552 R.J. Olsen- quitclaim deed twater right, 1930
      - 553 Alaska Salmon Co. and Jacobson- agreement, 1930
      - 554 Lewis L. Laska- contract, 1930
      - 555 C.P. Hall- grazing application, 1927-1934
    - Accounts 556 - 563, 1930 - 1937 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - 556 Louis Strauss- deed McGlaskan house, 1930
      - 557 Herring- pickling instructions; distribution lists, 1934-1937
      - 558 Dutch Harbor Dock as a public dock, 1930
      - 559 Pacific National Bank- Seattle, 1930-1931
      - 560 Transfer of Amaknah Island, 1930
      - 561 Aleutian Islands- fur production, 1933-1934
      - 563 Safe combination, 1930
    - Accounts 566 - 570, 1928 - 1931 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - 566 Aleutian Livestock Co., 1928-1929
      - 567 Aleutian Fur Co.- "Eunice" charter, 1931-193?
      - 568 Fishing contracts, 1931
      - 569 R.B. Patterson- agreement, 1931
      - 570 James Griffiths & Sons- contract for "El Cedro" trip tUnalaska, 1931
    - Accounts 571 - 579, 1919 - 1931 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - 571 Manson Construction and Engineering Co.- contract, 1931
      - 573 R.B. Patterson contract- restaurant and poolroom at Unalaska, 1931
      - 574 N. Gray- stock in Eureka Divide Mining Co., 1919-1929
      - 575 Roger V. Adams- agent at Unalaska, 1931
      - 576 J.W. Fletcher- agreement, 1931
      - 577 Paul Riggs- Fair poolroom, 1931
      - 578 A.H. Proctor- agent, contract, 1931
      - 579 Wells Fargo Bank and Union Trust Co., 1931
    - Accounts 580 -582, 1924 - 1931 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - 580 Hatch House at Unalaska, 1928-1931
      - 581 Dick Mathews- Unalaska, 1931
      - 582 Martha Bourke, 1924-1931
    - Account 583 Invoice tW.J. Erskine Co.- merchandise shipped to Unalaska, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Accounts 584 - 594, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - 584 Annual statement of assets, 1931
      - 585 List of vessels wrecked or in distress in Bering Sea and North Pacific, 1927-1931
      - 586 "Amoknah"- details of new engine, 1932
      - 587 Directors' authorization, 1931
      - 588 H.H. Lindhe, 1932
      - 589 Standard Oil Co., 1932
      - 590 Dr. E. Hulten- letter of credit from Royal Consulate of Sweden, 1932
      - 594 Eddie Lee- contract, 1932
    - Accounts 595 - 601, 1925 - 1933 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - 595 Yukon Consolidated- re: Sulpher Creek claims, 1925-1932
      - 596 Herring pack at Dutch Harbor, 1932
      - 598 Paul E. Toplift- cook at Unalaska, 1933
      - 599 "Einar Beyer"- contract, 1933
      - 600 "El Cedro"- charter by J. Griffiths & Sons, 1933
      - 601 John H. Gage- contract, 1933
    - Account 602: Statement of assets and liabilities, 1932-1939 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Accounts 603 - 604, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - 603 Alaska Salmon Co. and John A. Yatchmeneff, 1933
      - 604 C.C. Euback- agreement, 1933
    - Accounts 605 - 615, 1926 - 1938 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - 605 Herring pack contracts, 1933
      - 606 John A. Rockas of Seattle- agreement, 1933
      - 607 Kanaga Ranching Co. mortgage, 1932
      - 608 Standard Oil Co.-contract, 1934
      - 612 Umnak natives and Kanaga Ranching Co.- agreement, 1926
      - 613 Jack and Grace Martin tA.C.Co.- deed, 1933-1938
      - 615 Instructions tthe captain of the MS "Ruth", 1933
    - Accounts 616 - 624, 1923 - 1935 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - 616 Permit 108 Kiska Island, 1923
      - 617 Herring contracts, 1934-1935
      - 618 Kiska Harbor and Dutch Harbor- description of facilities, 1934
      - 619 Russian Church- agreement, 1934
      - 621 James Lavigne, 1934
      - 622 Atka Island native agreement, 1934
      - 624 Natomas stock- sale, 1934
    - Account 625: Alcohol Control file, 1934 - 1937 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Accounts 626 - 629, 1932 - 1935 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - 625 Alcohol control file, 1934-1937
      - 626 Campbell & Dougal - assignment to A.C.Co., 1935
      - 627 Mr. Fred Wagner - contract (cook), 1935
      - 629 Ray Burner Co., 1932-1935
    - Account 246, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Account 276, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Account 281, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Account 285, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Account 295, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Account 299, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Account 380, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Account 416, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Account 420, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Account 429, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Account 430, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Account 434, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Account 435, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Account 442, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Account 503, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Account 429 (Box 19.2, Folder 1)
    - Account 438 (Box 19.2, Folder 2)
    - Account 454 (Box 19.2, Folder 3)
    - Account 464 (Box 19.2, Folder 4)
    - Account 467 (Box 19.2, Folder 5)
    - Account 474 (Box 19.2, Folder 6)
    - Account 508 (Box 19.2, Folder 7)
  - Subseries C. Financial Reports from Unalaska, 1936 - 1940
    - Payroll, 1936 Sept. - 1936 Nov. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Payroll, 1936 Dec. - 1937 Jan. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Credit sales journal sheets [1 of 2], 1936 Sept. - 1940 Aug. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Credit sales journal sheets [2 of 2], 1936 Sept. - 1940 Aug. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Journal sheets, 1936 Sept. - 1937 Apr. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Journal sheets, 1937 May - 1937 Oct. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Journal sheets, 1937 Nov. - 1938 July (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Journal sheets, 1938 Aug. - 1939 June (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Journal sheets, 1939 July - 1940 Feb. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Journal sheets, 1940 Mar. - 1940 Sept. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Journal sheets, 1940 Oct. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Oil sales, 1936 June - 1940 Aug. (Box 15, Folder 4)